♪ I'm going down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Going down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"howdy, neighbor" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Okay, children, we have
a special guest today --
a woman recruiting young people
for a national choir tour.
Now, I know that choir tours
are totally stupid and lame,
but please give her
your full attention.
Go ahead.
Uh, thank you,
Mr. Garrison.
How are we all doing
today?
I can't hear you!
I said,
"how are we all doing?"
[farts]
Eric Cartman,
you say "excuse me"!
Okay.
Go ahead.
Children, we are
a national choir called
"Getting Gay With Kids."
We're gonna do a big tour
down in Central America
to help save the rainforest,
and you can be a part of it.
Mrph rmhmhm rm.
- [laughter]
Kenny McCormick, you speak
when you're spoken to!
Go ahead.
You see, we take kids
from all over the country
and put them in a choir
where we sing and dance
[yawns]
to raise awareness about
our vanishing rainforests.
Did you know over
10,000 acres of rainforest
are bulldozed every year?
That's right, and over
30% of the world's oxygen
is made
in the rainforest.
Miss Stevens: So,
who wants to join the fun?
What if you don't
have any rhythm?
Excuse me?
- Like my friend Kyle.
He's Jewish so
he doesn't have any rhythm.
Shut up, fat-ass!
- Choirs suck.
Kyle Broflovski,
you watch your language!
Eric Cartman,
you be nice to people!
Stan Marsh,
you mind your manners!
Kenny McCormick,
you pay attention!
[exhales] Go ahead.
Well, that's all,
really.
So if anyone is interested
in seeing the rainforest
and joining our choir,
I'll leave information packets
up front.
That's good. We need
some more toilet paper.
[laughter]
Alright,
that does it!
Mr. Mackey: I am tired
of seeing you in my office.
You get sent here
every day, Craig.
I know.
Why can't you behave?
I don't know.
What do you have to say
for yourself?
Well, I'll tell you what,
young man,
you're gonna be held back
a grade if you don't--
Did you just flip me off?!
- No.
Yes, you did.
You just flipped me the bird.
Now, see, this is exactly
what I'm talking about.
If you don't shape up, m'kay,
and get your head straight--
There! You just
flipped me off again!
No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did!
And until you stop
flipping people off,
you can just go back
to the waiting room, m'kay?
Next!
Well, well, well,
if it isn't Stan, Kyle,
Kenny, and Eric.
Hey, Craig.
- Hey, don't flip me off,
you son of a bitch!
Sit down, boys.
Let's see, what did Mr. Garrison
send you in here for?
"The boys were being rude
while a choir teacher
was giving
some stupid presentation."
It's just some dumb
activist kids' choir thing.
Young man,
"Getting Gay With Kids"
is not dumb, m'kay?
It just so happens that
I'm on the board of directors.
Dude, all those choirs
are the same.
They don't even really sing.
They use prerecorded tapes.
Well, guess what, boys?
I think "Getting Gay With Kids"
is just what you need.
I'm gonna sign up
all four of you.
What?!
- You can't do that!
Mrph rm!
Mrph rm, mrph.
I think this will be
very good for you.
But we don't even care
about the rainforest.
And that's exactly
why you need to go, m'kay?
Please, Mr. Mackey,
we'll be good!
Don't send us
to that old kids' choir!
Have mercy, Mr. Mackey!
Be safe, Kyle.
Bring me something back
from the rainforest.
Oh, no, the rainforest
is very fragile.
We must take only pictures
and leave only footprints.
Oh,
I didn't realize.
Did you know
that right now,
bulldozers are tearing down
thousand of acres
of rainforest
every day?
Ah, man, this is
gonna suck donkey balls.
Please, don't make me go on
a choir tour, mom! Please!
Stan,
you should be excited.
I would love to see
the rainforest.
Besides, your dad and I
need some time alone.
Noooo!
Okay, children,
that's all of us.
We're ready to head for
the Latin-American nation
of Costa Rica,
a country filled
with virgin rainforest.
Whoopee.
And you must be Eric Cartman.
I've heard about you.
You don't respect nature
or other cultures.
Yeah, pretty much.
Well, I'm gonna change
the way you think, kiddo.
My name's Kelly.
Mrph rm rmphm.
- Lenny?
Mrph rmphm!
- Johnny?
Rmphm!
- Oh.
Now, we've got a long trip
ahead of us,
so let's take the opportunity
to learn our choreography.
The nightmare begins.
[Latin-American music plays]
Oh, look, children!
I think
we're entering San José,
which is the capital
of Costa Rica.
Oh, this is so exciting!
Oh, my God, dude!
Look how dirty
and crappy everything is!
Eric, Costa Rica
is a third-world country.
These people are much poorer
than those in the U.S.
Why the hell
don't they get jobs?
Hey! Why don't you people quit
slacking off and get a job?!
What's wrong with you?!
Go to college!
Eric, sit down!
You gotta be firm
with these people
or they just slack off and
be poor forever, right, Kenny?
Hey, maybe that's it, Kenny.
Maybe you're Costa Rican.
That's why your family's
so poor.
Mrph rmhmhm rm.
- Your family isn't poor?
Wow, dude,
look over there!
Wow!
Costa Rican prostitutes!
Hey, look at the prostitutes,
you guys!
[Latin accent]
What are you looking at, man?
[Latin accent] Yeah,
why don't you take a picture?
Okay. Cleek!
Miss Stevens:
Eric, sit down!
Kids, this is the Costa Rican
Capitol building.
This is where
all the leaders
of the Costa Rican government
make their--
Oh, my God, it smells
like ass out here!
Alright,
that does it!
Eric Cartman, you respect
other cultures this instant!
I wasn't saying anything
about their culture.
I'm just saying
their city smells like ass.
Wow, seeing a place
like this
really makes you appreciate
living in America, huh?
Mrph rm.
You may think
that making fun
of third-world countries
is funny,
but let me--
I don't think
it's funny.
This place is overcrowded,
smelly, and poor.
That's not funny.
That sucks.
Eric, will you please, please,
just keep your mouth shut
while we present ourselves
to the Costa-Rican president?
Why?
Because I'll buy you
some ice cream if you do.
[laughing] Oh!
Well, it was a long trip,
but the children are very
excited to sing tomorrow.
¿Qué?
Uh, we're the choir
that-that was sent
from the United States.
¿Qué?
We're the group singing
for the "Save the Rainforest"
summit tomorrow?
Oh, dear,
where's Mr. Mackey?
He should've been here
by now.
Children, do any of you
speak Spanish?
Don't you dare!
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, thank goodness you're here.
I don't speak any Spanish.
Oh, no problem.
Usted es choir
de estados unidos, muy bien.
Oh, oh--
"Save the Rainforest."
Yes!
[speaking Spanish]
He says, "Pablo here will take
you on a rainforest tour."
Oh, boy!
Mr. Presidente,
round up
your subjects outside.
We have a special gift
for you--
The gift... of song.
¿Qué?
Alright, children,
let's get in our rows quickly
so we can begin.
Did you remember all
the choreography, Lenny?
Mrph rmhmhm rm.
Hello, everybody!
This is just
a little rehearsal for tomorrow,
so we may be
a little rusty.
[chuckling]
♪ Doo-doo-dee-doo ♪
♪ Zada-doo-dee-wow ♪
Boys: ♪ There's a place
that is magical ♪
♪ And full of rain ♪
Girls: ♪ But now it needs help
because it is in pain ♪
All: ♪ Cleaning the earth
is a mighty big chore ♪
♪ We're spreading awareness
like never before ♪
♪ Getting Gay With Kids
is here ♪
♪ To spread the word
and bring you cheer ♪
♪ Let's save the rainforest,
what do you say? ♪
♪ Being an activist
is totally gay ♪
♪ And someday, if we work hard,
boys and girls ♪
♪ There'll be nothing
but rainforest ♪
♪ Covering
the entire world ♪
♪ World! ♪
♪ Getting Gay With Kids
is here ♪
♪ To spread the word
and bring you cheer ♪
♪ Getting Gay With Kids
is here ♪
♪ So save the rainforest ♪
♪ Totally gay ♪
♪ It's totally gay! ♪
[boom box clicks off]
Great job, gang!
You were really
all over the place, Kyle.
Thanks.
I told you Jewish people
don't have rhythm.
Fuck off, Cartman!
No, dude, I think Cartman
might actually be right.
No!
That's a stereotype!
Dude, maybe you really
don't have any rhythm.
This is now secondary
rainforest we're entering.
Notice the canopy
of foliage.
Oh, it's everything
I ever dreamed it would be!
Damn,
it's hot out here.
Aah! Snake!
No, dude,
that's a branch.
Oh. Aah! Snake!
No, that's
the same branch again.
Oh.
The rainforest
is very delicate,
and we must take steps
to protect it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Take steps,
blah, blah, blah.
We hear this a million times
back up in the States.
Here, look--
these are squirrel monkeys,
endangered inhabitants
of the rainforest.
Wow, isn't he neat,
Lenny?
Bad! Bad monkey!
Eric, what the heck
are you doing?!
I'm asserting myself.
It's tough love,
just like my Mr. Kitty.
When he's bad, I say,
"that's a bad Mr. Kitty!"
And I smack him
on the head!
And here is
a three-toed sloth.
It's bad--
that's a bad three-toed sloth!
Eric, for God's sake,
knock it off!
Respect my authoritah!
Well, Mr. Pedro,
this was a great tour,
but I guess we should be
heading back.
We have a big concert tomorrow,
don't we, kids?
Yeah!
I wish we could've seen
the yanogapa.
What's the Yanogapa?
The Yanogapa
are a gentle native people
that live
in the rainforest,
but bulldozers
are destroying their homes.
Soon, they will have
nowhere to go.
So we must stop
bulldozing the rainforest --
Oh, God,
here she goes again!
Aah!
- Stanley, what is it?
Snake!
[all gasping]
Oh, yes, this is what
we call a coral snake.
Notice the red markings.
Quite an amazing creature.
Aah!
What's the matter,
little boy?
He's a little wuss.
What's it look like?
I'm just scared
of snakes.
No, no,
you must remember,
this snake is more afraid of us
than we are of it.
Aah!
[groans]
Oh, my God!
Yeah, that snake is really
scared of us, alright.
Jesus Christ!
Is he dead?
Dude!
My guess
would be "yes."
Oh, no! God, no!
Now, don't panic, children.
Bad!
That's a bad snake--
aah!
Maybe we came from that way.
No... No.
Let's try this way.
Lenny, do you think
we're gonna be okay?
Mrph rmhmhm rm.
That's good.
Can I tell you something?
Mrph rm.
- I think I like you.
Mrph?!
Yeah, I think we
communicate really well.
Mrph rmhmhm rm!
- No, that's not good.
Mrph rmh rmphm?
No. See, if I start to
like you too much,
I'm only going to
get my heart broken,
'cause we live on opposite ends
of the country.
Once this choir tour
is over,
we'll never see
each other again,
and that would
devastate me!
So I can't have
any feelings for you!
I just can't, Lenny!
- Mrph!
Oh, children,
the sun is setting.
We have to find our way
out of here, quick!
[thunder crashes]
Okay, okay.
Everything is just fine,
kids.
Now, it is important
that we all stick together.
Is everybody still here?
Boy: I'm not.
Who's not?
Me.
Lenny, will you
hold my hand?
I don't want to get
emotionally attached, though.
Oh, my God, dude!
I just saw Tony Danza!
No, you didn't just see
Tony Danza, Stanley.
[rooster crowing]
Bueno. Bueno.
[speaking Spanish]
Stan: Dude,
we're totally lost.
We're gonna die out here.
- Kelly: We are?
Don't worry, Kelly,
we're gonna find our way
out of the rainforest
and make it back
to the concert in time.
We just need to respect
our mother rainforest,
and she will respect us.
Mrs. Stevens, you have
a bug on your back.
Oh, really?
Could you brush it off?
[roaring]
Um, no.
Whoa! Oh, my God!
Get it off me!
For the love of God,
get it off me!
Oh, my God!
[insect roaring]
Okay, children,
we must understand
that the insects
of the rainforest
help the delicate balance
of life here.
[roaring]
Oh, my God!
The rainforest sucks.
I want to go home.
Me too!
[children grumbling]
Shh, children.
Let's try to listen to
what the rainforest tells us.
And if we use our ears,
she can tell us
so many things --
Aah!
There's a dude here.
Oh, thank goodness!
Hello, sir, we are lost.
[chuckling]
Can you help us?
¿Qué?
Let me try, let me try.
We are from America--
A-mer-ica.
We are lost
and very hungry.
Necesito burritos.
I don't want a burrito,
I want a taco... supreme.
A taco.
I want two tostadas
with mild sauce.
Two tostadas...
Boys, not every Spanish person
eats tacos and burritos.
That's a stereotype.
Children, he wants us
to follow him.
Oh, thank goodness!
I think this ordeal
is over.
This doesn't look
very safe.
Yeah, I think we should
get the hell out of here.
Now, kids, let's be
a bit more open-minded.
I've read all about this
in Newsweek.
This is a people's army.
They are fighting
the fascist policies
of their fascist government.
Oh, hello.
Do you speak, uh, English?
Who are you?
- Oh, wonderful!
We were lost, and it is
such a great coincidence
we found you.
We're here to protest
the government-sanctioned raping
of your rainforest.
We are fighters,
just like you.
Could you help us
get back to San José?
Um...oh, I know!
Perhaps you would like a gift.
Well, we have only
one gift to give--
the gift of song.
[groaning]
♪ Doo-doo-dee-doo ♪
♪ Zada-doo-dee-wow ♪
Boys: ♪ There's a place
that is magical ♪
♪ And full of rain ♪
Kyle, for the love of God,
do the right choreography.
All: ♪ Cleaning the earth
is a mighty big chore ♪
♪ We're spreading awareness
like never before ♪
Oh, Kyle, please!
♪ Getting Gay With Kids
is here ♪
Enough!
Well, we hope that
our gift of song
has warmed your hearts.
We're not getting gay
with any kids, okay?
Uh, yeah, so... do you have
a phone we could use?
Yes, we have a phone.
It's right over there,
next to the 12-person jacuzzi.
[laughter]
Now, get out of here
before we kill you!
If it's because of the little
Jewish boy's choreography--
Hey!
You whacked Americans
make me sick.
You waste food, oil,
and everything else
because you're so rich, and then
you tell the rest of the world
to save the rainforest
because you like
its pretty flowers.
[gunfire]
Aah!
Rápido! Rápido!
Miss Stevens:
Run, children, run!
Hello? Anybody?
Help!
Wow, look at
the pretty flower.
Oh, no, no, no, Jake.
That fragile flower
is very delicate.
[muffled] Aah!
Ow, it hurts!
Aah!
[crying] I want to go home!
I hate the rainforest!
Mrph rmhmhm rm.
Oh, Lenny, hold me.
No,
I can't get attached.
But I do like you.
- Mrph rmh rmphm.
But you're only
going to leave me.
Mrph rmhmhm rm!
We're here live
in San José, Costa Rica,
where hundreds of
rich Americans have gathered
for the "Save the
Rainforest" summit.
Everyone is here so they can
feel good about themselves
and act like they aren't
the ones responsible
for the rainforest's
peril.
That's right, Bob,
and, of course,
the main attraction today
is the darling kids' choir
"Getting Gay With Kids,"
all of whom must be
backstage preparing
at this very moment.
[birds squawking]
Oh, there's just
no end to this place.
I think maybe
we're going in circles.
Oh, dear God!
The summit starts in an hour.
I'm going to lose my job.
[roaring]
Aah!
This is bull crap.
I am not following this
stupid hippie around anymore.
Where are you going?
- I'm going this way.
Young man,
I am the adult here,
and I say
you go this way!
Look,
you can stay over nah,
but I'm going over nah!
Young man,
I have had it!
No, no, no --
you nah, me nah.
Screw you guys!
I'm going home.
Good! You deserve to die,
you little bastard!
Eric, we have to
stay together!
God damn stupid
hippie activist.
I should be home
nestled on the couch
with my Mr. Kitty right now
watching "Fat Albert"
cartoons...
Yes! I knew it!
I'm saved!
Hey, maybe Cartman
was right.
Yeah, it happened
once before.
No, the spirit of Maya
has told me to go this way.
Mister, you gotta help me!
I'm starving to death.
What are you doing here,
little boy?
I was with my class,
and we got lost rainforest,
and I need some food!
I'm fading fast!
Lost in the rainforest?
Oh, my Lord!
Where are
all the others?
Food!
I have to have food!
Oh, my God! Get this child
some food, quick!
Chicken wings.
Chicken wings!
Medium spicy.
Crowd: [chanting]
Start the show! Start the show!
[laughing]
Oh, God,
this is a nightmare!
We're never going to
make the festival.
Hey, look over there.
Isn't that smoke?
Let's go, quickly!
Hey, it's a fire. That means
there must be people.
[rustling]
Children,
it's the Yanogapa!
Do not be afraid.
We are not here to tear down
your rainforest.
[speaking
native language]
Look how they live in peace
with all living things.
Gentle, noble...
Run for your lives children!
- Holy crap!
[yanogapa chanting
in native language]
Jesus Christ!
- Run, run, run!
[roaring]
Aah!
Aah! Lenny!
What the hell?
I'm sinking.
It's quicksand!
[chanting quickens]
All we ever heard
growing up
was "save the rainforest,"
"the rainforest is fragile."
Yeah, fragile my ass!
Larry, if we
make it out of this,
I want to be
your girlfriend.
Even if we do live
in different places,
I don't care.
Mrph rmhmhm rm.
[Yanogapa chanting
in native language]
Okay, just what the heck
is going on here, people?
[chanting continues]
[chanting slowly]
Aaaah!
Oh, no!
That big thing is going to
make love to Miss Stevens!
Alright, that does it!
God damn,
stupid-ass rainforest!
This place fucking sucks!
I was wrong!
Fuck the rainforest!
I fucking hate it!
Now she figures it out.
Quick!
Everybody help the children!
Hyah!
[chanting]
Wow!
Dude, bulldozers rule!
Come on, let's get you
back to civilization!
All: Hooray!
Hooray, children!
How did you know
where we were?
Your little friend
helped me out.
Eric?
Who'd you expect?
Merv Griffin?
What exactly are you guys
doing out here
with all this
construction equipment?
We're clearing out
big sections of the rainforest
for a lumberyard.
Really?
That's great!
You mean,
you don't mind?
No, I hate
the rainforest.
You go right ahead and plow down
this whole fucking thing.
That's swell!
Okay, Lenny, so,
in order for our long-distance
relationship to work,
we'll have to call each other
every other day.
Mrph rmhmhm rm.
Aah!
Aah! Lenny, no!
Oh, my God!
They killed Kenny!
You bastards!
What?! Who?!
Who killed him?!
They did.
Who's "they"?
You know, "they".
They're--
they're bastards.
Well, don't just stand there!
Help him!
What?
Help... him?
Ugh!
Come on, Benny!
Breathe!
Breathe,
you son of a bitch!
[coughs]
Whoa, dude!
And now,
here to teach us
about the rainforest
is "Getting Gay With Kids."
Does everybody remember
the new lyrics?
And...
♪ Doo-doo-dee-doo ♪
♪ Zada-doo-dee-wow ♪
Boys: ♪ There's a place
called the rainforest ♪
♪ That truly sucks ass ♪
All: ♪ Let's knock it all down
and get rid of it fast ♪
Boys: ♪ You say,
"save the rainforest" ♪
♪ But what do you know? ♪
All: ♪ You've never been
to the rainforest before ♪
♪ Getting Gay With Kids
is here ♪
♪ To tell you things
you might not like to hear ♪
♪ You only fight these causes
'cause caring sells ♪
♪ All you activists can go
fuck yourselves ♪
That was so inspiring.
What a wonderful
message.
Boy: ♪...Boys and girls ♪
Kelly: ♪ There'll be no more
rainforests ♪
♪ Left in
the entire world ♪
♪ World ♪
♪ Getting Gay With Kids
is here ♪
♪ To spread the word
and bring you cheer ♪
♪ Getting Gay With Kids
is here ♪
♪ Let's knock down
the rainforest ♪
♪ What do you say? ♪
♪ It's totally gay ♪